export default data = [
  {
      question: "As computers are getting less expensive, they are _______ used in schools and offices today.",
      options: ["widely","expectedly","consciously","influentially"],
      correct_option: "widely"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Chang always tries to answer all questions from his students. He will not _____ any of them even if they may sound stupid.",
      options: ["reform","depress","ignore","confirm"],
      correct_option: "ignore"
  },
  {
      question: "Irene does not throw away used envelopes. She ____ them by using them for taking telephone messages.",
      options: ["designs","recycles","disguises","manufactures"],
      correct_option: "recycles"
  },
  {
      question: "Cheese, powdered milk, and yogurt are common milk ____.",
      options: ["produces","products","productions","productivities"],
      correct_option: "products"
  },
  {
      question: "Although he is a chef, Roberto _____ cooks his own meals.",
      options: ["rarely","bitterly","naturally","skillfully"],
      correct_option: "bitterly"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to the yearly bonus system, the 100 ________ positions in this high-tech company have attracted many applicants from around the island.",
      options: ["loyal","evident","typical","vacant"],
      correct_option: "loyal"
  },
  {
      question: "If you want to borrow magazines, tapes, or CDs, you can visit the library. They are all ______ there.",
      options: ["sufficient","marvelous","impressive","available"],
      correct_option: "available"
  },
  {
      question: "The fire in the fireworks factory in Changhua set off a series of powerful  _________ and killed four people.  ",
      options: ["explosions","extensions","inspections","impressions"],
      correct_option: "impressions"
  },
  {
      question: "A good government official has to ________ the temptation of money and make the right decision.",
      options: ["consist","insist","resist","persist"],
      correct_option: "consist"
  },
  {
      question: "The drug dealer was ________ by the police while he was selling cocaine to a high school student.",
      options: ["threatened","endangered","demonstrated","arrested"],
      correct_option: "demonstrated"
  },
  {
      question: "The rise of oil prices made scientists search for new energy resources to ______ oil.",
      options: ["apply","replace","inform","persuade"],
      correct_option: "persuade"
  },
  {
      question: "Without much contact with the outside world for many years, John found many technological inventions _____ to him.",
      options: ["natural","common","foreign","objective"],
      correct_option: "common"
  },
  {
      question: "The medicine you take for a cold may cause _____; try not to drive after you take it.",
      options: ["incident","violence","bacteria","drowsiness"],
      correct_option: "bacteria"
  },
  {
      question: "To gain more ______, some legislators would get into violent physical fights so that they may appear in TV news reports.",
      options: ["publicity","reputation","significance","communication"],
      correct_option: "communication"
  },
  {
      question: "To live an efficient life, we have to arrange the things to do in order of _____ and start with the most important ones.",
      options: ["authority","priority","regularity","security"],
      correct_option: "authority"
  },
]
